Hello friends, I am Ajay Singh, a
CSP Certified Financial Planner. Today, I will
tell you about a wonderful policy that you might not have imagined. The
country's leading bank, Indian Bank, has
tied up with India's most reputed health insurance company, Max Bupa,
and has brought this policy to us, called
Machel Plus Super
Top Policy. Yes, today we will talk about the
Super Top Policy,
how it works, and what
benefits we can get from it. To understand all these things,
let's learn
about the Machel Plus Super Top Policy. The Machel Plus Top Policy
is a boon that Indian Bank has given to its salary
account holders. You will also know one thing
for all of you:
from birth till death, one thing that
follows us like a shadow is disease. As soon as
we are born, we
start getting injections or vaccines to protect us from diseases,
and many times in our lives,
we have to fight these diseases.
You must have heard this film dialogue
that death is infamous for no reason.
Life gives pain. Many times in life we
come to such a point where our
troubles increase. This often
happens when we or any of our family members is
affected by some disease or virus
and in that condition it
works like adding fuel to the fire. The cost of treatment of this disease,
if we have to be
hospitalized even for the treatment of a small disease, then a
good portion of our savings is
spent on the treatment of that disease. Then if the
disease is big or of a serious nature, then
you can understand that all your savings
or sometimes your land gets sold.
But you can avoid all these unwanted things.
If you need help for yourself and your family,
buy a medical policy. Today we will
tell you about such a policy which will
remove all your worries. This policy
is for those people who have a
corporate salary account in Indian Bank or Allahabad Bank.
But this video is
also for those people who do
not have a salary account in Indian Bank or Allahabad Bank.
Because those who have a salary account in Indian Bank,
they have already
taken this policy.  If you are standing in line, you can also
come to Indian Bank and open your zero balance
account and get it.
Now we will talk about what is Super To position and
how it works. Super To
works on a contract of Kochi duty.
To get Super To political benefits,
you must have a basic help and security.
Before you listen to this policy
and take it, I would like you to
take a basic help and security of up to Rs 12 lakh for yourself, only after that this
policy will work very well for your sons. Let us
understand this with an example, let us assume that you have
kept a help and security of Rs 2 lakh for your family.
You can cover your hospital bill up to Rs 2 lakh with this,
whose premium will come to you for only four to
five rupees. But if you
ever face such a disease or accident
where your hospital bill is going to be
Rs 5 lakh, 10 lakh or 15 lakh, then
such mathematics. A person with a good income may
face a lot of challenge in spending this money and it is possible that
they may have to take the help of their relatives or friends.
But what if
you have to
spend only ₹10 to cover the expenses of Kushal ranging from 2 lakh to 1500000 rupees, then how about
you can get super toe poles up to 15 lakh rupees
in the court of question for only one and a half rupees,
for this you only have to
open your zero balance account in Indian Bank,
now I will tell you about the
premiums coming according to different family members, this
policy is for two plus two men, stud alt and two z, this policy
is available at an annual premium of 1939 rupees,
for this doodle trend untrained this policy
is available at a premium of 1500,
that finger toot only to result two alt, if you have
members in your family then
you will get this policy for 1235 rupees and right now
if you are single and unmarried then
you can buy this policy from Indian Bank branch at an annual premium of only 70, that
if you go to the market and buy the same condition
same combination policy  If you purchase it, you will
find that the premium will range from ₹2,000 to
₹20,000. Furthermore,
if you are older, the premium will
increase accordingly. However, the standard
premium has been set for all.
Let us explore some of the features of this policy.
This policy will
cover all major hospital expenses
such as nursing in-charge, medical
practitioner fees, medicines, physiotherapy,
blood transfusion, operation theatre recharge,
surgery room rent, ICU charges without any application fee,
and all sub-limits. These
combinations are covered under this policy after 15 days of purchasing the policy.
This policy will cover 536 diseases
for which you will not have to be admitted to the hospital.
You
can also get their treatment at the facility, and
transplants in these facilities have also been
included in this policy. Thirty days
free end sewerage post placement in medical
expenses and constipation saver mode. A limit of ₹4000 has been kept on the list to
cover some specific diseases.
You can refer to this list.  Read it carefully before and after taking it
so that there is no confusion
about which diseases will be covered and for how long.
You can estimate the popularity of this policy
from the fact that the
General Manager of Indian Bank himself
first took this policy for himself and after that, as soon as the
rest of the officers read this policy, they could
not refuse this policy.
Let us know which officers of Indian Bank have
taken this policy
[Music]
So what are you waiting for, open a
zero balance salary account in your bank branch
and take advantage of it.
Thank you.